好的，大家开始吧
all right everybody let's get started
今天的报纸，我四天是Aurora姑姑，这是关于如何
today the paper four days I'm is aunt
Aurora paper which is all about how to
获得高性能可靠的数据库作为云基础架构的一部分
get a high-performance reliable database
going as a piece of cloud infrastructure
并且本身是建立在Amazon本身提供的基础架构之上
and itself built out of infrastructure
that Amazon itself makes available so
之所以要阅读本文，是因为首先
the reason why we're reading this paper
is that first of all it's a very
亚马逊最近成功的云服务成功，许多客户都在使用它
successful recent cloud service from
Amazon a lot of their customers use it
它以自己的方式展示了一个从聪明中获得巨大回报的例子
it shows sort of in its own way an
example of a very big payoff from clever
设计表对性能进行了总结，表明：
design table one which sort of
summarizes the performance shows that
相对于其他系统，该系统并没有很好地解释
relative to some other system which is
not very well explained the paper claims
使交易吞吐量提高三十五倍，这是
to get a thirty five times speed up in
transaction throughput which is
非常令人印象深刻的这篇论文还探讨了
extremely impressive this paper also
kind of explores the limits of how well
您可以使用通用存储来提高性能和容错能力
you can do for performance and fault
tolerance using general-purpose storage
因为他们基本上是论文的主题之一，却放弃了通用
because one of the themes of the papers
they basically abandoned general-purpose
他们从原来使用亚马逊自己设计的设计切换到存储
storage they switch from a design in
which they were using their Amazon's own
通用存储基础架构认为它还不够好，
general-purpose storage infrastructure
decided it was not good enough and
基本建立了完全基于应用程序的存储
basically built totally
application-specific storage
此外，该论文对结果产生了一些小窍门
furthermore the paper has a lot of
little tidbits about what turned out to
在这个云基础架构世界中非常重要
be important in this and the kind of
cloud infrastructure world so before
谈论极光，我想花些时间回头
talking about aurora i want to spend a
bit of time kind of going over the back
历史或我对导致设计的故事的印象是什么
history or what my impression is about
the story that led up to the design of
极光，因为这是您所知道的mf--亚马逊想到的方式
aurora because it's you know the sort of
m f-- way that amazon has in mind that
您应该建立自己的云客户应该在
you ought to build that their cloud
customers ought to build databases on
亚马逊的基础设施，所以一开始亚马逊基本上
amazon's infrastructure so in the
beginning amazon had basically their
第一个提供云产品以支持想要构建的人
very first offering cloud offering to
support people who wanted to build
网站，但首先使用亚马逊的硬件，并在亚马逊的机房中
websites but using Amazon's hardware and
in Amazon's machine room their first
显然，弹性云也提供了称为ec2的产品，并且
offering was something called ec2
for elastic cloud apparently too and the
这里的想法是，亚马逊拥有装满服务器的大型机房，
idea here is that Amazon had big machine
rooms full of servers and they ran
服务器上的虚拟机监视器，他们会将虚拟机出租
virtual machine monitors on their
servers and they'd rent out virtual
机器给他们的顾客和他们的顾客，那么你会知道租一个
machines to their customers and their
customers would then you know rent a
一堆虚拟机并运行Web服务器和数据库以及其他任何东西
bunch of virtual machines and run web
servers and databases and whatever ever
他们需要在这些ec2实例中运行的所有其他内容，因此其中一个的图片
all else they needed to run inside these
ec2 instances so the picture of one
物理服务器看起来像这样的亚马逊我们控制虚拟机监视器
physical server looked like this Amazon
we control the virtual machine monitor
在这个硬件服务器上，然后会有一堆客人，一堆ec2
on this hardware server and then there'd
be a bunch of guests a bunch of ec2
实例，每个实例都租给了不同的云客户
instances each one rented out to a
different cloud customer each of these
只会运行像Linux这样的标准操作系统，然后您就会知道
would just run a standard operating
system like Linux and then you know a
Web服务器或数据库服务器，它们相对便宜
web server or maybe a database server
and these were relatively cheap
相对容易设置，并且作为一项非常成功的服务，因此只需一点细节
relatively easy to set up and as a very
successful service so one little detail
对我们来说最重要的是，一开始您获得存储的方式
that's extremely important for us is
that initially the way you get storage
如果您租用ec2实例，则您拥有存储空间的方式是：
the way you've got storage if you rented
an ec2 instance was that every one of
他们的服务器有一个磁盘连接，一个物理磁盘连接，每个
their servers had a disk attached a
physical disk attached and each one of
他们租给客户的这些实例会让我们知道
these instances that they rented to
their customers will get us you know a
磁盘的一部分，所以他们说是本地连接的存储，您得到了一些
slice of the disk so they said locally
attached storage and you got a bit of
本地连接的存储，其本身就像是模拟的硬盘
locally attached storage which itself
just look like a hard drive an emulated
硬盘驱动器到虚拟机
hard drive to the virtual machine guests
ec2非常适合用于无状态Web服务器的Web服务器
ec2 is like perfect for web servers for
stateless web servers you know your
客户使用其网络浏览器将连接到一堆租用的ec2
customers with their web browsers would
connect to a bunch of rented ec2
运行Web服务器的实例，如果突然添加了更多客户
instances that ran a web server and if
you added all of a sudden more customers
您可以立即从中租用更多ec2实例
you could just instantly rent more ec2
instances from
亚马逊并在其上启动Web服务器，这是一种扩展您的规模的简单方法
Amazon and fire up web servers on them
and sort of an easy way to scale up your
能够处理Web负载，因此对Web服务器非常有用
ability to handle web load so it was
good for web servers
但是人们在ec2实例中运行的另一件事是数据库
but the other main thing that people ran
in ec2 instance this was databases
因为通常网站是由一组无状态的网络服务器构成的，
because usually a website is constructed
of a set of stateless web servers that
每当他们需要获取永久数据时，请与后端数据库进行对话，以便
anytime they need to get out permanent
data go talk to a back-end database so
您将获得的可能是外部世界中的一堆客户端浏览器
what you would get is is maybe a bunch
of client browsers in the outside world
在亚马逊网络基础设施之外，然后是许多ec2网络服务器
outside of Amazon's web infrastructure
and then a number of ec2 web server
您所需的实例数，以运行网站逻辑
instances as many as you need it to run
the sort of logic of the website this
现在位于Amazon内部，然后还有一些通常也是一个ec2实例
this is now inside Amazon and then also
some also typically one ec2 instance
运行数据库，您的Web服务器将与您的数据库实例通信，并且
running a database your web servers
would talk to your database instance and
不幸的是，它要求它读写数据库中的记录
ask it to read and write records in the
database unfortunately ec2 wasn't
完美的是，它与运行数据库几乎一样适合运行数据库
perfect was it nearly as well-suited to
running a database as it was to running
Web服务器，最直接的原因是存储或排序
web servers and the most immediate
reason is that the storage or the sort
ec2数据库实例获取存储的主要简单方法是在本地
of main easy way to get storage for your
ec2 database instance was on the locally
附加磁盘连接到数据库实例的任何硬件
attached disk attached to whatever a
piece of hardware your database instance
当前正在运行，实际上硬件崩溃了，然后您也丢失了
was currently running on in fact
hardware crashed then you also lost
可以访问硬盘驱动器上的任何内容，因此如果它是硬件
access to whatever what is on its hard
drive so if it's a hardware that it was
实际实现Web服务器完全不会崩溃，因为
actually implementing a web server
crashed no problem at all because
真正没有状态本身，您只是在新服务器上启动了新的Web服务器
there's really keeps no state itself you
just fire up a new web server on a new
ec2实例（如果它是运行硬件的ec2实例）崩溃了
ec2 instance if the ec2 instance it's a
hardware running it crashes have become
如果数据存储在本地，则不可用
unavailable you have a serious problem
if the data is stored on the locally
附加磁盘，因此至少在最初没有太多帮助
attached disk so initially at least
there wasn't sort of a lot of help for
做到这一点效果很好的一件事是，亚马逊确实提供了这一点
doing this one thing that did work out
well is that Amazon did provide this
一种用于存储称为s3的大数据块的大型方案，您可以
sort of large scheme for storing large
chunks of data called s3 and you could
拍摄快照如果需要，可以拍摄Prius定期快照
take snapshots you could take Prius
periodic snapshots if you need a basis
状态并存储在s3中，并将其用于备份灾难恢复，但是您
state and stored in s3 and use that for
sort of backup disaster recovery but you
知道定期快照的样式意味着您将丢失更新
know that style of periodic snapshots
means you're gonna lose updates that
定期备份之间可以发生
happen
between the periodic backups all right
所以接下来发生的事情与Aurora的种类有关
so the next thing that came along that's
that's relevant to the sort of Aurora
数据库的故事是为了向客户提供磁盘
database story is that in order to
provide their customers with disks for
他们的ec2实例，如果出现更多故障，则不会消失
their ec2 instances that didn't go away
if there was a failure that is more sort
引入了容错的长期存储
of fault tolerant long-term storage was
guaranteed to be there Amazon introduced
称为EBS的服务，它代表弹性块存储
the service called EBS and this stands
for elastic block store
因此，使用EBS是一种服务，它查找的是ec2实例，
so with EBS is is a service that looks
to an ec2 instances it looks to one of
这些来宾虚拟机之一的实例就像是
these instances one of these guest
virtual machines just as if it were a
普通方式将硬盘格式化为硬盘但文件格式
hard drive an ordinary way you could
format it as a hard drive but a file
像ext3之类的系统，或者您喜欢在这个东西上使用的任何Linux文件系统
system like ext3 or whatever Linux file
system you like on this on this thing
看起来就像是一个硬盘驱动器，但实际上它是客人
that looks to be guest just like a hard
drive but the way it's actually
实现是作为存储服务器的复制对，因此这是本地
implemented is as a replicated pair of
storage servers so this is the local
这是Mike的本地存储之一，如果当EBS出现时，您可以
this is one of local storage with Mike
if when EBS came out then you could you
可以租一个e BS卷，这东西看起来像普通的
could rent an e BS volume which this
thing that looks just like an ordinary
硬盘驱动器，但实际上是成对实现的，所以这些是EBS服务器
hard drive but it's actually implemented
as a pair so these are EBS servers a
一对EBS服务器，每个服务器都附带一个硬盘驱动器，因此如果您的软件是
pair of EBS servers each with an
attached hard drive so if your software
在这里，也许您正在运行数据库，而数据库挂载是其中之一
here maybe you're running a database now
and your databases mount's one of these
当数据库服务器未写入时，EBS卷作为其存储
EBS volumes as its storage when the
database server doesn't write what that
实际上意味着通过网络发送和使用链的权利
actually means is that the right to send
out over the network and using chain
我们上周谈到的复制是正确的，您首先知道
replication which we talked about last
week you're right is you know first
写入到支持您的第一台CBS服务器上的EBS服务器
written to the EBS server one on the
first CBS server that's backing your
卷，然后第二个，最后您得到答复，类似
volume and then the second one and
finally you get the reply and similarly
当您进行读取时，我想您会进行一些链式复制，
when you do a read I guess some chain
replication you'll be the last of the
链，因此现在在ec2实例上运行的数据库有可用的存储系统
chain so now database is running on ec2
instances had available a storage system
实际上可以幸免于崩溃或您知道硬件已死
that actually would survive the crash of
or the you know death of the hardware
如果这台物理服务器死了，他们将继续运行
that they were running on if this
physical server died you could just get
另一个ec2实例启动您的数据库并将其附加到
another ec2 instance fire up your
database and have it attached to the
与旧数据库版本相同的旧EBS卷
same old EBS volume that the sort of
previous version of your database was
附加到它，它将看到所有旧数据，就像被
attached to and it would see all the old
data just as it had been left off by the
以前的数据库，就像您将硬盘驱动器从一台计算机移动到另一台计算机一样
previous database just like you moved a
hard drive from one machine to another
因此，对于需要永久保存的人来说，EBS确实是一笔不错的交易
so EBS was like really a good deal for
people who need it to keep permanent
像运行数据库的人这样说，这对
state like people running databases one
thing to that is sort of important for
关于EBS的事实是，它不是一个随时共享的系统
us about EBS is that it's really it's
not a system for sharing at any one time
只有一个ec2实例，只有一个虚拟机可以装载给定的EBS卷，因此
only one ec2 instance only one virtual
machine can mount a given EBS volume so
EBS卷是在庞大的机队中实施的，您可能知道数百或
the EBS volumes are implemented on a
huge fleet of you know hundreds or
亚马逊上有磁盘的任何存储服务器，它们都是您所知道的
whatever storage servers with disks at
Amazon and they're all you know
每个人的EBS卷都存储在这个庞大的服务器池中，但是每个
everybody's EBS volumes are stored on
this big pool of servers but each one of
每个PPS卷只能由一个ec2实例使用仅一个客户
each PPS volume can only be used by only
one ec2 instance only one customer all
EBS仍然是一大进步，但仍然存在一些问题，因此
right still EBS was a big step up but it
had still has some problems so there's
还有一些不尽如人意的事情是，如果
still some things that are not quite as
perfect as it could be one is that if
您在EBS上运行数据库，最终会跨服务器发送大量数据
you run a database on EBS it ends up
sending large volumes of data across the
网络，这是呃，我们现在开始偷偷摸摸地看图
network and this is uh we're now
starting to sort of sneak up on figure
他们开始抱怨论文中的两个
two in the the paper where they start
complaining about how many just how many
如果在网络存储系统上运行数据库，则需要写
writes it takes if you run a database on
top of a network storage system so
EBS上的数据库最终产生了大量的网络流量，并且
there's the database on EBS ended up
generating a lot of network traffic and
该论文所暗示的论文中的一种是
one of the kind of things in the paper
that the paper implies is that they're
受CPU或存储空间限制的网络数量所限
as much network limited as they are CPU
or storage limited that is they pay a
大量关注减少Aurora纸张发送了大量
huge amount of attention to reducing the
Aurora paper sends a huge amount of
注意减少数据库生成的网络，并且似乎
attention for reducing the network
that the database generates and seems to
不必担心要消耗多少CPU时间或磁盘空间
be worrying less about how much CPU time
or disk space is being consumed that's a
暗示他们认为重要的是EBS的另一个问题是
sort of a hint at what they think is
important the other problem with EBS is
不太容错，事实证明，出于性能原因，我
not very fault tolerant it turns out
that for performance reasons they I'm
完成将始终将两个EBS和您的EBS卷的两个副本
done would always put both of the EBS
both of the replicas of your EBS volume
在同一个数据中心中，因此，如果您知道其中一台服务器，则会使单个服务器崩溃
in the same data center and so we have a
single server crashed if you know one of
您正在使用的两个EBS服务器崩溃了，因为您切换到了
the two EBS servers that you're using
crashed it's okay because you switch to
另一个，但根本没有任何故事，如果
the other one but there was just no
story at all for what happens if an
整个数据中心都关闭了，显然有很多客户
entire data center went down and and
apparently a lot of customers really
想要一个故事，使他们的数据能够在整个系统故障后幸存下来
wanted a story that would allow their
data to survive an outage of an entire
数据中心可能失去了网络连接，这是建筑物中的火灾
data center maybe it lost his network
connection it was a fire in the building
或整个建筑物的电源故障或人们真正想要的东西
or a power failure to the whole building
or something people really wanted to
如果他们愿意为自己的数据付出更多，至少可以选择
have at least the option if they're
willing to pay more of having their data
以一种隐藏的方式存储，即使有一个数据，我仍然可以做到这一点
stored in a way they hid they could
still get at it I'm even if one data
中心下降，亚马逊描述此问题的方式是
center goes down and the way that Amazon
described this there is that both an
实例及其EBS到EBS副本位于同一能力面纱能力区域
instance and its EBS to EBS replicas are
in the same ability veil ability zone
和亚马逊行话，可用区是一个特定的数据中心，
and an Amazon jargon an availability
zone is a particular data center and the
他们构建数据中心的方式通常是多个
way they structure their data centers is
that there's usually multiple
或多或少位于同一城市或相对接近的独立数据中心
independent data centers in more or less
the same city or relatively close to
彼此，所有多个可用区可能是两个或三个
each other and all the multiple
availability zones maybe two or three
彼此靠近的地方都通过冗余高速连接
that are near by each other are all
connected by redundant high speed
网络，因此总是有付款者或附近可用性的三倍
networks so there's always payers or
triples of nearby availability
可用性中心，我们会看到购买很重要，但
availability centers and we'll see the
buy that's important in a little bit but
至少对于EBS来说，是为了保持使用链复制的成本
at least for EBS in order to keep the
sort of costs of using chain replication
下来，他们要求两个副本位于同一可用区中
down they required the two replicas to
be in the same availability zone
好吧，在我进一步了解Aurora的实际工作方式之前
all right um before I dive into more
into how Aurora actually works it turns
为了了解它们，我们首先要了解设计的细节
out that the details of the design in
order to understand them we first have
对典型数据库的设计种类有相当多的了解，因为
to know a fair amount about the sort of
design of typical databases because what
他们采取的是某种数据库的主要机制，这是我的续集
they taken is sort of the main machinery
of a database my sequel as it happens
并以一种有趣的方式将其拆分，因此我们需要了解某种形式，但它
and split it up in an interesting way so
we need to know sort of what it but it
是一个数据库，所以我们可以理解他们是如何将其拆分的，所以这确实是一个
is a database does so we can understand
how they split it up so this is really a
一种数据库教程，实际上着重于实现所需的内容
kind of database tutorial really
focusing on what it takes to implement
交易使可恢复交易崩溃，所以我真正关心的是
transactions crashed recoverable
transactions so what I really care about
是事务和崩溃恢复，数据库中还有很多其他事情
is transactions and crash recovery and
there's a lot else going on in databases
但这确实是本文重要的部分，所以首先是什么
but this is really the part that matters
for this paper so first what's a
您知道的事务事务只是包装多个操作的一种方式
transaction you know transaction is just
a way of wrapping multiple operations on
也许是不同的数据，并声明那是全部
maybe different pieces of data and
declare in that that that's entire
操作顺序应向正在阅读或阅读的其他人显示为Tomic
sequence of operations should appear a
Tomic to anyone else who's reading or
编写数据，以便您可能会看到转置我们正在经营一家银行，而我们
writing the data so you might see
transposing we're running a bank and we
想要在不同帐户之间进行转帐，也许您会说我们
want to do transfers between different
accounts maybe you would say well we
会看到代码，或者您知道看到交易看起来像这样
would see code or you know see a
transaction looks like this is you have
清除您要成为的指令序列的开头
to clear the beginning of the sequence
of instructions that you want to be
交易中的原子交易，也许我们要从帐户Y转移资金
atomic in the in transaction maybe we're
going to transfer money from account Y
账户X，所以我们可能会看到我会假装X是约旦的银行结余
to account X so we might see where I'll
just pretend X is a bank balance Jordan
您可能会看到交易的数据库看起来像哦，我可以加10美元
the database you might see the
transaction looks like oh can I add $10
到X的帐户并从我的帐户中扣除相同的十美元
to X's account and
deduct the same ten dollars from my
帐户，交易到此结束
account and that's the end of the
transaction
我希望数据库只做它们两者，而不允许其他人偷偷摸摸
I want the database to just do them both
without allowing anybody else to sneak
并查看这两个语句之间的状态以及
in and see the state between these two
statements and also with respect to
如果在此处某处发生崩溃，则会崩溃
crashes if there's a crash at this point
somewhere in here we're going to make
确保崩溃和恢复后，整个交易要么
sure that after the crash and recovery
that either the entire transactions
值得的修改是可见的，或者没有一个是可见的，这就是我们的效果
worth the modifications are visible or
none of them are so that's the effect we
希望从交易中获得额外的人期望数据库
want from transactions there's
additionally people expect database
用户希望数据库会告诉他们告诉客户提交了
users expect that the database will tell
them tell the client that submitted the
交易，无论交易是否真正完成和完成，以及
transaction whether the transaction
really finished and committed or not and
如果交易已提交，我们希望客户期望该交易将
if a transaction is committed we expect
clients expect that the transaction will
即使数据库应该崩溃，永久性的持久性仍然存在。
be permanent will be durable still there
even if the database should crash and
重新启动一件事，这很重要，那就是这些
reboot um one thing it's a bit important
is that the usual way these are
实现的是，事务在使用前锁定每个数据
implemented is that the transaction
locks each piece of data before it uses
这样您就可以查看它们在锁定期间被锁定的x和y
it so you can view the they're being
locks x and y for the duration of the
交易，并且仅在交易最终提交后才释放
transaction and these are only released
after the transaction finally commits
众所周知，这是永久的，如果您在某些事情上很重要
that is known to be permanent this is
important if you for some of the things
如果您要了解本文中的某些详细信息，实际上只能
that you have to if you some of the
details in the paper really only makes
如果您意识到数据库实际上正在锁定其他对
sense if you realize that the database
is actually locking out other access to
交易期间的数据，实际如何
the data during the life of a
transaction so how this actually
实现了原来的数据库
implemented it turns out the database
至少由简单数据库模型组成，其中数据库是
consists of at least for the simple
database model where the databases are
通常编写为在单个服务器上运行并且知道一些存储
typically written to run on a single
server with you know some storage
直接连接，而Aurora纸正在玩的游戏
directly attached and a game that the
Aurora paper is playing is sort of
仅对该软件进行了适度的修订，以便在更多软件上运行
moving that software only modestly
revised in order to run on a much more
复杂的网络系统，但出发点是我们只是假设我们拥有一个
complex network system but the starting
point is we just assume we have a
附加到磁盘的数据库存储这些数据的磁盘结构
database with a attached to a disk the
on disk structure that stores these
记录是某种类似于b树的索引结构
records is some kind of indexing
structure like a b-tree maybe so
有一些纸质数据页面，这些页面使我们知道
there's a sort of pages with the paper
calls data pages that holds us you know
数据库的真实数据，您知道这可能是多余的余额，
real data of the of the database you
know maybe this is excess balances and
这是明智的平衡，这些数据页通常包含很多记录
this is wise balance these data pages
typically hold lots and lots of records
而X和y通常只是
whereas X and y are typically just a
couple bites on some page in the
数据库，因此磁盘上有实际数据，磁盘上还有
database so on the disk there's the
actual data plus on the disk there's
正确的日志还是沃尔玛，正确的日志是
also a right ahead log or wal and the
right ahead logs are a critical part of
为什么系统要在数据库服务器内部容错
why the system is gonna be fault
tolerant inside the database server
有数据库软件，数据库通常具有页面缓存
there's the database software the
database typically has a cache of pages
它是从您最近执行的磁盘读取的
that it's read from the disk that it's
recently used when you execute a
事务实际上执行这些语句的含义
transaction what that actually executes
these statements what that really means
您是否知道x等于x加10变成运行时间的原因是
is you know what x equals x plus 10
turns into the runtime is that the
数据库从磁盘读取保存X的当前页面，并向其添加10，但是
database reads the current page holding
X from the disk and adds 10 to it but so
直到事务提交，它才在
far until the transaction commits it
only makes the modifications in the
本地缓存不在磁盘上，因为我们不想公开我们不想
local cache not on the disk because we
don't want to expose we don't want to
写在磁盘上，并且该部分可能会暴露部分事务，因此
write on the disk yet and the part
possibly expose a partial transaction so
而当数据库时，但是之前，因为数据库想要排序
while then when the database but before
because the database wants to sort of
预先清除完整的交易，以便在交易完成后可供软件使用
pre to clear the complete transaction so
it's available to the software after a
崩溃并在恢复过程中允许数据库修改实数
crash and during recovery before the
database is allowed to modify the real
磁盘上的数据页首先需要添加描述
data pages on disk its first required to
add log entries that describe the
事务，因此必须先进行排序，然后才能提交所需的事务
transaction so it has to in order before
it can commit the transaction it needs
将一整套完整的预先登录项放入磁盘上的正确预先登录
to put a complete set of log ahead
entries in the right ahead log on disk
我正在描述所有数据库修改，所以在这里假设
I'm describing all the data bases
modification so let's suppose here that
x和y开始为500，y开始为750，我们要执行
x and y start out as say 500 and y
starts out as 750 and we want to execute
提交之前和写入数据库页面之前的此事务
this transaction before committing and
before writing the pages the database is
通常至少要添加3个日志记录1这可以说是
going to add at least typically 3 log
records 1 this that says well as part of
这笔交易我正在修改X，它的旧值为500，请留出更多空间
this transaction I'm modifying X
and it's old value is 500 make more room
这是在日志上的记录，因此每个日志条目可能会说这是我的值
here this is the on dis log so each log
entry might say here's the value I'm
修改这里是旧值，我们要添加，这里是新值，说五
modifying here's the old value and we're
adding and here's the new value say five
十，所以这是一个日志记录，另外一个4y可能是旧值，我们是750
ten so that's one log record another 4y
may be old value is 750 we're
减去10，所以新值是740，然后在数据库中
subtracting 10 so the new value is 740
and then when the database if it
实际上设法在交易崩溃之前到达交易结束
actually manages to get to the end of
the transaction before crashing its
要写一个提交记录说，通常这些都用一些标签标记
gonna write a commit record saying and
typically these are all tagged with some
使用交易ID进行排序，以便恢复软件最终将知道
sort with a transaction ID so that the
recovery software eventually will know
此提交记录如何引用这些日志记录是
how this commit record refers to these
log records yes
在一个简单的数据库中就足以存储新值并说得好
in a simple database will be enough to
just store the new values and say well
这是一场崩溃，我们将重新应用所有新值是最重要的原因
it is a crash we're gonna just reapply
all the new values the reason most
严肃的数据库存储着旧的和新的价值，就是赋予它们自由
serious databases store the old as well
as a new value is to give them freedom
甚至对于长期交易而言甚至是长期牵引
to even for a long-running traction for
a long-running transaction even before
事务完成后，数据库可以自由编写
the transaction is finished it gives the
database the freedom to write the
用新值740将更新后的页面更新到磁盘，例如从
updated page to disk with the new value
740 let's say from the from an
未完成的事务，只要将日志记录写入磁盘，然后
uncompleted transaction as long as it's
written the log record to disk and then
如果在提交之前发生崩溃，恢复软件总是说得很好
if there's a crash before the commit the
recovery software always say aha well
该交易从未完成，因此我们必须撤消所有交易
this transaction never finished
therefore we have to undo all of its
更改和这些值这些旧值是您需要订购的值
changes and these values these old
values are the values you need in order
撤消已部分写入数据页的事务，因此
to undo a transaction that's been
partially written to the data pages so
Aurora实际上使用撤消重做日志记录来撤消部分应用
the aurora indeed uses undo redo logging
to be able to undo partially applied
事务还可以，所以如果数据库设法做到了
transactions okay so if the database
manages to get as far as getting the
磁盘上的事务日志记录，并且提交记录标记已完成
transactions log records on the disk and
the commit record marking is finished
那么它有权向我们所说的交易客户申请
then it is entitled to apply to the
client we said the transactions
提交数据库可以回复客户端，并且可以保证客户端
committed the database can reply to the
client and the client can be assured
它的交易将永远可见，现在是两个交易之一
that its transaction will be sort of
visible forever and now one of two
事情发生了，数据库服务器并没有崩溃，然后最终崩溃了
things happens the database server
doesn't crash then eventually so it's
这些X＆Y记录在其缓存中修改为510和740，最终
modified in its cache these these X&Y
records to be 510 and 740 eventually the
数据库会将其缓存的更新块写入磁盘上的实际位置
database will write it's cached updated
blocks to their real places on the disk
通过重写，您知道这些是树节点或其他东西，然后是数据库
over writing you know these be tree
nodes or something and then the database
可以重用日志的这一部分，因此数据库倾向于对此有所延迟
can reuse this part of the log so
databases tend to be lazy about that
因为他们喜欢积累您知道的东西，也许会有很多更新
because they like to accumulate you know
maybe there'll be many updates to these
缓存中的页面最好在被更新之前积累很多更新
pages in the cache it's nice to
accumulate a lot of updates before being
如果在写日期之前数据库服务器崩溃，则被迫写入磁盘
forced to write the disk if the database
server crashes before writing the day
将这些页面写入磁盘，以便它们仍然具有旧值，然后
writing these pages to the disk so they
still have their old values then it's
保证当您重新启动恢复软件
guaranteed that the recovery software
when you restart that
降级扫描日志，查看这些记录以了解交易，
debase scan the log see these records
for the transaction see that that
事务已提交，并将新值应用于存储数据和
transaction was committed and apply the
new values to the to the stored data and
这称为重做，它基本上具有事务中的所有权限，因此
that's called a redo it basically does
all the rights in the transaction so
简而言之，这就是事务数据库的工作方式，所以这是一种
that's how transactional databases work
in a nutshell and so this is a sort of
例如我的续集数据库的非常简短的版本
very extremely abbreviated version of
how for example the my sequel database
Aurora就是基于这种称为开源软件的东西
works that an Aurora is based on this
open source software thing called
称为我的续集的数据库，它确实进行崩溃恢复事务和崩溃
database called my sequel which does
crash recovery transaction and crash
以这种方式恢复就可以了，所以亚马逊发展的下一步更好
recovery in much this way ok so the next
step in Amazon's development a better
为其云客户提供更好的数据库基础架构称为
and better database infrastructure for
its cloud customers is something called
RDS和我只是在谈论RDS，因为事实证明，即使
RDS and I'm only talking about RDS
because it turns out that even though
该论文没有完全提及它，该论文中的图2基本上是一个
the paper doesn't quite mention it
figure 2 in the paper is basically a
RDS的描述，所以RDS正在进行的事情是这是第一次尝试
description of RDS so what's going on
and RDS is that it was a first attempt
获取在多个可用区中复制的数据库，以便
to get a database that was replicated in
multiple availability zones so that if
整个数据中心发生故障，您可以取回数据库内容
an entire data center went down you
could get back your database contents
不会失去任何权利，因此与RDS的交易就是您拥有
without missing any rights so that deal
with RDS is that there's one you have
一个ec2实例即数据库服务器
one ec2 instance that's the database
server
您只有一个，而您只想运行一个数据库，它将存储其数据
you just have one you just want to
running one database it stores its data
页面并基本上仅以此记录日志，而不是在其存储的本地磁盘上
pages and log just basically with this
instead of on the local disk its stores
它们在EBS中，因此无论何时数据库执行日志写或页面写或
them in EBS so whenever the database
does a log write or page write or
不论这些权利实际上属于这两个EBS卷，还是
whatever those rights actually go to
these two EBS volumes EBS replicas in
如此等等，这是在每个可用区域之外的一个可用区域中
addition so and so this is in one
availability zone in addition for every
写道数据库软件可以做到亚马逊将透明地没有
write that the database software does
Amazon would transparently without the
数据库甚至意识到必然发生这种情况，也将这些权利发送给
database even realizing necessarily this
was happened also send those rights to
在第二台计算机的第二个可用性区域中进行的特殊设置
a special set up in a second
availability zone in a second machine
房间-从图2转到显然是一台单独的计算机或ec2
room - just going from figure 2 to
apparently a separate computer or ec2
实例或仅是镜像的工作便会写入主数据库
instance or something whose job was just
a mirror writes that the main database
这样做，那么另一种镜像服务器将只复制这些权限
did so this other sort of mirroring
server would then just copy these rights
到第二对EBS服务器，因此通过此RDS设置进行此设置
to a second pair of EBS servers and so
with this set up with this RDS set up
这就是数字-每次数据库追加到日志或写入日志时
and that's what figure - every time the
database appends to the log or writes to
它必须将其页面之一的数据发送到这两个副本中
one of its pages it has to the data has
to be sent to these two replicas has to
通过网络连接在另一个可用区域上发送
be sent on the network connection across
the other availability zone on the other
城镇的一侧发送到此镜像服务器，然后将其发送到
side of town sent to this mirroring
server which would then send it to it's
两个单独的EBS副本，然后最终此答复将返回，
two separate EBS replicas and then
finally this reply would come back and
然后只有这样才能正确完成DAT bc AHA我的写信
then only then with the right be
finished with a DAT bc AHA my writes
完成了，我知道这个日志记录真的是附属的吗
finished I can you know count this log
record it was really being appendage of
日志或其他什么使RDS安排使您更容易
the log or whatever
so this RDS arrangement gets you betcha
更好的容错能力，因为现在您拥有完整的最新副本
better fault tolerance because now you
have a complete up-to-date copy of the
数据库就像在单独的可用性中查看它们所有的最新写入
database like seeing them all the very
latest writes in a separate availability
即使您知道大火烧毁了整个数据中心的繁荣，您也可以
zone even if you know fire burns down
this entire data center boom you can
削弱了您可以在新实例中运行数据库和第二个可用性
weaken you can run the database in a new
instance and the second availability
区域并完全不丢失数据是
zone and lose no data at all yes
嗯，我不知道该怎么回答，我的意思是那不是他们所做的，
um I don't know how to answer that I
mean that is just not what they do and
我的猜测是，对于大多数电动汽车客户来说
my guess is that it would be that for
most EVs customers it would be too
缓慢地在两个独立的数据中心之间转发所有权限，我不是
painfully slow to forward every right
across two separate data center I'm not
真的确定发生了什么，但我认为主要的回答是他们没有这样做，
really sure what's going on but I think
the main answers they don't do that and
对于EBS的工作方式来说，这也是一种解决方法
this is sort of a a little bit of a
workaround for the way EBS works too
一种棘手的BS，实际上是生产和使用现有的EBS
kind of tricky BS and actually producing
and sort of using the existing EBS
基础设施没有变化，我稳定的人选择这是非常极端的
infrastructure unchanged I stableman
chose this turns out to be extremely
昂贵，或者您可能认为昂贵
expensive or anyway it's expensive as
you might think
您知道我们正在写入大量数据，因为您甚至知道
you know we're writing fairly large
volumes of data because you know even
这笔交易似乎只是修改了两个整数，例如
this transaction which seems like it
just modifies two integers like maybe
八个字节，或者我不知道那十六个谁只知道几个字节的数据
eight bytes or I don't know what sixteen
who knows only a few bytes of data are
在这里进行了修改，直到数据库读取和
being modified here what that translates
to as far as the database reading and
写磁盘是我实际上这些日志记录也很小
writing the disk is I actually these log
records are that also quite small so
这两个日志记录本身可能只有几十个字节，所以
this these two log records might
themself only be dozens of bytes long so
很好，但是实际数据页的读取和写入很可能是
that's nice but the reads and writes of
the actual data pages are likely to be
比每个十几个字节要大得多，因为每个页面
much much larger than just a couple of
dozen bytes because each of these pages
将会是您知道8 KB或16 KB或一些相对较大的
is going to be you know eight kilobytes
or 16 kilobytes or some relatively large
编号文件系统或磁盘块的大小，这意味着仅读取和
number the file system or disk block
size and it means that just to read and
当需要更新数据页面时，请写下这两个数字
write these two numbers when it comes
time to update the data pages there's a
现在将大量数据推送到本地连接的磁盘上
lot of data being pushed around on to
the disk a locally attached disk now
速度相当快，但我想他们开始发送时发现的是
it's reasonably fast but I guess what
they found is when they start sending
整个网络上8千字节的大量写操作已经用完了
those big 8 kilobyte writes across the
network that that used up too much
要支持的网络容量，因此此配置此图2
network capacity to be supported and so
this arrangement this figure 2
安排显然太慢了
arrangement evidently was too slow yes
因此，在此图中此图设置了数据库服务器未知的信息
so in this in this figure to set up the
you know unknown to the database server
每次调用写入侵蚀其EBS磁盘时，每次写入的副本都会被复制
every time it called write erode its EBS
disk a copy of every write went over
跨可用区，并且必须写入到写入
across availabilities zones and had to
be written to the was written to the
这两个EBS服务器，然后进行确认，然后才进行写入
both of these EBS servers and then
acknowledged and only then did the write
似乎已完成数据库，所以我真的不得不等待所有秋天
appear to complete to the database so I
really had to wait for all the fall for
副本进行更新，并将数据通过链接发送到另一个
copies to be updated and for the data to
be sent on the link across to the other
可用区，就表一而言，您首先要关注
availability zone and you know as far as
table one it's concerned that first
性能表之所以
performance table the reason why the
镜像的续集之所以慢的原因要比
reason why the slow the mirrored my
sequel line is much much slower than the
Aurora产品线基本上是通过这些设备发送大量数据
Aurora line is basically that it sends
huge amounts of data over these
相对较慢的网络链接，这就是性能问题
relatively slow Network links and that
was the problem that was the performance
他们确实试图解决的问题，所以这对于容错很有用，因为
problem they're really trying to fix so
this is good for fault tolerance because
现在我们有第二个副本和另一个可用区，但这是一个坏消息
now we have a second copy and another
availability zone but it was bad news
像Aurora一样提高性能，这之后的下一步是Aurora
for performance all right the way Aurora
and the next step after this is Aurora
并在那里设置高级视图，就是我们仍然有一个数据库服务器
and to set up there the high level view
is we still have a database server
尽管现在它正在运行亚马逊提供的自定义软件，所以我可以
although now it's running custom
software that Amazon supplies so I can
从亚马逊租用Aurora服务器，但不是我没有在以下位置运行我的软件
rent an Aurora server from Amazon but
it's not I'm not running my software on
我正在租用一台运行Amazon Aurora数据库软件的服务器，
it I'm renting a server running Amazon's
Aurora database software on it rent an
来自他们的Aurora数据库服务器，它只是其中的一个实例
Aurora database server from them and
it's it's just one instance it sits in
一些可用性区域，关于它的方式有两个有趣的事情
some availability zone and there's two
interesting things about the way it's
首先要设置的是，您知道的数据基本上可以代替EBS
set up first of all is that the data you
know it's replacement basically for EBS
现在涉及六个副本-在三个可用区中的每个可用区中
involves six replicas now
- in each of three availability zones
具有超强的容错能力，因此每次数据库复杂时，我们都会讨论
for super fault tolerance and so every
time the database complicated we'll talk
但基本上是在数据库写入时或在数据库写入时读取时
but basically when the database writes
or reads when the database writes it's
我们不确定它的管理方式，但它或多或少需要发送
we're not sure exactly how its managed
but it more or less needs to send a
必须以一种或另一种方式写入所有六个副本
write one way or another writes have to
get sent to all six of these replicas
制作的关键，所以这看起来像更多的副本，你知道为什么不这样做
the key to making and so this looks like
more replicas gosh you know why isn't it
慢一点，为什么不比以前只有四个的计划慢
slower why isn't it slower than this
previous scheme which only had four
复制品，答案是唯一的是
replicas and the answer to that is that
what's being the only thing being
通过网络写入的是日志记录，因此这实际上是
written over the network is the log
records so that's really the key to
成功之处在于从副本的意义上讲遍历这些链接的数据
success is that the data that goes over
these links in the sense of the replicas
这只是日志记录日志条目的日志，如您所见，您知道一个日志条目
it's just the log records log entries
and as you can see you know a log entry
在这里你至少知道，这是一个简单的例子，现在不是
here you know at least and this is a
simple example now it's not quite this
很小，但实际上并不需要超过几十个字节
small but it's really not vastly more
than a couple of dozen bytes needed to
存储我们正在编写的数据的旧值和新值，以便
store the old value and the new value
for the piece of data we're writing so
日志条目往往很小，而当您知道数据库时，
the log entries tend to be quite small
whereas when the database you know we
有一个数据库，它认为它正在写入本地磁盘并且正在更新
had a database that thought it was
writing a local disk and it was updating
它的数据页通常非常庞大，就像在
its data pages these tended to be
enormous like doesn't really say in the
纸张，我认为不超过8 KB，所以在这里进行设置
paper I don't think that eight kilobytes
or more so this set up here was sending
每笔交易都将多个8 KB页面发送到
for each transaction was sending
multiple 8 kilobyte pages across to the
副本，而此设置只是将这些小日志条目发送给更多
replicas whereas this set up is just
sending these small log entries to more
副本，但日志条目比8k页小得多，因此
replicas but the log entries are so very
much smaller than 8k pages that it's a
净表现赢了，所以这就是他们的重要见解之一
net performance win okay so that's one
this is like one of their big insights
当然只是日志条目中的一个后果是它们的存储
is just in the log entries of course a
fallout from this is that their storage
系统现在不是很通用，这是一个存储系统，
system is now not very general purpose
this is a storage system that
知道如何处理我的续集日志条目，不只是您知道
understands what to do with my sequel
log entries right it's not just you know
EBS是一个非常通用的用途，只是模拟到您正确阅读的磁盘上
EBS was a very general purpose just
emulated to disk you read them right
区块除了区块之外什么都不懂
block's doesn't understand anything
about anything except for blocks this is
一个真正了解它位于主机下方的存储系统
a storage system that really understands
that it's sitting underneath the
数据库，所以他们要做的一件事就是放弃通用存储
database so that's one thing they've
done is ditched general-purpose storage
并切换到特定于应用程序的存储系统
and switched to a very application
specific storage system
我还要详细介绍的另一件事是，它们不需要
the other big thing I'll also go into in
more detail is that they don't require
所有六个副本都应确认该权限，以便使用数据库
that the rights be acknowledged by all
six replicas in order for the database
服务器继续运行，而数据库服务器可以持续到法定人数
server to continue instead the database
server can continue as long as a quorum
而事实证明，只要这些服务器中的任何四个服务器做出响应，
and which turns out to be for as long as
any four of these servers responds so if
这些可用性区域之一处于脱机状态，或者可能是网络连接
one of these availability zones is
offline or maybe the network connection
速度很慢，甚至可能只是这些服务器的运行速度很慢
to it is slow or maybe even just these
servers just happen to be slow doing
目前，我们正在尝试编写数据库服务器的其他内容可以
something else at the moment we're
trying to write the database server can
基本上忽略了服务器中速度最慢或最慢的两个服务器
basically ignore the two slowest or the
two most dead of the server's when it's
正确地做，所以只需要六分之四的确认即可
然后它可以继续，所以这个仲裁方案是另一个大技巧
and then it can continue and so this
quorum scheme is the other big trick
他们用来帮助​​他们在更多可用区域中拥有更多副本，但没有
they use to help them have more replicas
in more availability zones and yet not
付出巨大的性能损失，因为他们不必等待所有的人
pay a huge performance penalty because
they never have to wait for all of them
只是六个副本中最快的四个，所以其余的讲座是
just the four fastest of the six
replicas so the rest of the lecture is
首先要解释法定人数，然后是日志条目，然后是
gonna be explaining first quorums and
then log entries and then this idea of
基本上只发送日志条目表一总结了结果
just sending log entries basically table
one summarizes the result if you look at
通过从他们发送大数据的这种体系结构切换到表一
table one by switching from this
architecture in which they send the big
数据页面到此Aurora模式的四个位置，仅将日志条目发送到
data pages to four places to this Aurora
schema sending just the log entries to
六个副本，它们的性能比其他副本高出惊人的35倍
six replicas they get a amazing 35 times
performance increase over some other
系统，您可以在这里了解该系统，但是通过玩这两个技巧，
system you know this system over here
but by playing these two tricks and
纸不是很好地解释了多少性能是由于
paper is not very good about explaining
how much of the performance is due to
法定人数以及多少是由于仅发送日志条目而导致的
quorums and how much is due to just
sending log entries but anyway you slice
它的改善性能是35倍
it 35
times improvement performance is very
对他们的顾客和对他们来说都是值得尊敬的，当然是非常有价值的
respectable and of course extremely
valuable to their customers and to them
这就像是变革性的，我相信许多亚马逊客户都可以
and it's like transformative I am sure
for many of Amazon's customers all right
好吧，我首先要详细谈的是他们的法定人数
okay so the first thing I want to talk
about in in detail is their quorum
安排他们实际上是法定人数的意思，所以首先是法定人数
arrangement what they actually mean by
quorums so first of all the quorums is
关于这个容错的所有容错的安排
all about the arrangement of
fault-tolerant of this fault-tolerant
存储，因此值得考虑一下其容错能力
storage so it's worth thinking a little
bit about what their fault tolerance
目标，所以这就像他们希望能够实现的容错目标
goals were so this is like fault
tolerance goals they wanted to be able
即使一个可用区是读写的，也可以执行权限
to do rights even if one reads and
writes even if one availability zone was
完全死了，所以即使他们想成为，他们也会写信给你
completely dead so they're gonna write
you know even with they wanted to be
即使有一个可用的空闲区域再加上一个其他的可用区域，也能够读取
able to read even if there was one dead
availability zone plus one other dead
服务器，其原因是可用性区域可能处于脱机状态
server and the reason for this is that
an availability zone might be offline
很长一段时间，因为也许你知道遭受洪灾或
for quite a while because maybe it's you
know was suffered from a flood or
几天或一周或几秒钟的故障
something and while it's down for a
couple of days or a week or something
人们准备好洪水带来的损失我们现在依靠的是
well people prepare the damage from the
flood we're now reliant on just you know
服务器和其他两个可用区（如果其中一个应该）
the servers and the other two
availability zones if one of them should
下去，我们仍然不希望这是一场灾难，所以他们将能够
go down we still we don't want it to be
a disaster so they're going to be able
即使有一个可用的空闲区域也可以写一个
to write with one even with one dead
availability zone they furthermore they
希望能够使用一个无效的可用区域和另一个无效的区域进行读取
wanted to be able to read with one dead
availability zone plus one other dead
服务器，因此他们希望仍然能够阅读您的知识并获得正确的信息
server so they wanted to be able to
still read you know and get the correct
数据，即使有一个可用的可用区加一台其他服务器
data even if there was one dead
availability zone plus one other server
实时可用区已经死了，所以您知道我们必须
and the live availability zones were
dead so you know they we have to sort of
认为他们知道自己的生意是理所当然的
take take it for granted that they know
what their they know their own business
而且这真的是您知道如何
and that this is really
you know kind of a sweet spot for how
容错，你想成为嗯，此外我已经提到他们想要
fault-tolerant you want to be um and in
addition I already mentioned they want
我可以从一个更高的位置上摆脱短暂的复制品
to be able to taller to sur ride out
temporarily slow replicas I think from a
很多资料很明显，例如，如果您阅读和编写EBS，
lot of sources it's clear that the if
you read and write EBS for example you
始终无法始终获得高性能，有时几乎没有
don't get consistently high performance
all the time sometimes there's little
出现故障是因为网络的某些部分过载或某些
glitches because maybe some part of the
network is overloaded or something is
进行软件升级或其他操作，而且它暂时变慢，因此他们希望成为
doing a software upgrade or whatever and
it's temporarily slow so they want to be
能够在瞬态瞬态缓慢或可能的情况下继续前进
able to just keep going despite
transient transiently slow or maybe
短暂无法使用的存储服务器，最终要求是
briefly unavailable storage servers and
a final requirement is that if something
如果存储服务器出现故障，则在时间上有点争夺
if a storage server should fail it's a
bit of a race against time before the
下一个存储服务器总是会失败，这不是统计数据
next storage server fails sort of always
the case and it's not the statistics are
不如您希望的那样有利，因为通常您基本上会购买
not as favorable as you might hope
because typically you buy basically
因为服务器故障通常不是独立发生的，例如
because server failure is often not
independent like the fact that one
服务器停机通常意味着出现以下情况的可能性大大增加
server is down often means that there's
a much increased probability that
您的另一台服务器很快就会宕机，因为相同的硬件可能
another one of your servers will soon go
down because it's identical Hardware may
从同一家公司被收购后同一生产线
be bought from the same company came off
the same production line one after
另一个是一个缺陷，其中一个极有可能反映在
another and so a flaw and one of them is
extremely likely to be reflected in a
缺陷和另一缺陷，所以人们总是紧张不安，有一个失败的男孩
flaw and another one so people always
nervous off there's one failure boy
很快就会出现第二次故障，在这样的系统中，
there could be a second failure very
soon and in a system like this well it
事实证明，在这些仲裁系统中，您只能恢复一点点
turns out in these quorum systems you
know you can only recover it's a little
有点像筏，只要没有太多的副本失败，您就可以恢复，所以
bit like raft you can recover as long as
not too many of the replicas fail so
他们真的需要快速，我们复制它们是一台服务器
they really needed to have fast we
replicate them that is of one server
似乎永远死了，我们希望能够以最快的速度生成新副本
seems permanently dead we'd like to be
able to generate a new replica as fast
尽可能从其余复制品中我指的是快餐复制品
as possible from the remaining replicas
I mean a fast food replication
这些是偷窥者提出的主要容错目标，并且通过这种方式
these are the main fault tolerance goals
the peeper lays out and by the way this
讨论仅涉及存储服务器，您知道它们的故障
discussion is only about the storage
servers and you know what their failure
角色太激动了，你知道失败的原因如何恢复，这是一个
character is too excited you know the
failures how to recover and it's a
完全独立的主题，如果数据库服务器发生故障并且Aurora具有
completely separate topic what to do if
the database server fails and Aurora has
通知数据库服务器的一套完全不同的机制失败
a totally different set of machinery for
noticing a database servers fail
创建在新实例上的新数据库服务器中运行的新实例
creating a new instance running in a new
database server on the new instance
这很激烈，这不是我现在要谈论的
which is intense it's not what I'm
talking about right now we'll talk about
稍后，它会建立一个存储系统
it a little bit later on right now it's
just gonna build a storage system that's
很多地方是存储系统可以容错的地方，所以他们使用了
a lot that's where the storage system is
fault tolerant okay so they use this
这个叫做法定人数的想法，现在我要描述一下
idea called quorums and for a little
while now I'm going to describe the sort
可以追溯到70年代后期的经典仲裁概念
of classic quorum idea which is dates
back to the late 70s so this is quorum
复制仲裁复制我将向您介绍此仲裁或抽象仲裁
replicate quorum replication I'm gonna
describe to you this or abstract quorum
想法他们使用了我要解释的变体以及背后的想法
idea they use a variant of what I'm
gonna explain and the idea of behind
仲裁仲裁系统应能够构建提供故障的存储系统
quorum quorum systems is to be able to
build storage systems that provide fault
使用复制进行容错存储，并确保即使某些
tolerance storage using replications and
guarantee that even if some of the
复制失败，则您的读取仍将看到最新的写入，通常
replicas fail your that reads will still
see the most recent writes and typically
仲裁系统是将get系统和
quorum systems are sort of simple
readwrite systems put get systems and
他们通常不直接支持更复杂的操作，而您可以
they don't typically directly support
more complex operations just you can
读取您可能有对象，可以读取对象，或者可以覆盖整个对象
read you could have objects you can read
an object or you can overwrite an entire
对象，所以这个想法是如果您要编写或者您有n个副本
object and so the idea is you have n
replicas if you want to write or you
必须让你必须要写你必须确保你写
have to get you have to in order to
write you have to make sure your write
被W确认，其中W小于副本的n个，因此W
is acknowledged by W where W is less
than n of the replicas so W
权利，您必须将每个权利发送给这些W是副本，如果您要
right you have to send each right to
these W are the replicas and if you want
要进行读取，您必须至少从我们的副本中获取输入的读取信息
to do a read you have to get input read
information from at least our replicas
因此，典型的设置非常重要，首先是
and so a typical setup that's so well
first of all the key thing here is that
必须将W和我们设置为相对于结束，以便您达到W服务器的任何定额
W and our have to be set relative to end
so that any quorum of W servers that you
设法发送的权利必须与任何法定人数重叠
manage to send a right to must
necessarily overlap with any quorum of
我们的服务器，任何将来的读者都可以从中读取，所以这意味着
our servers that any future reader might
read from and so what that means is that
我们的加号W必须大于n，以便任何W服务器必须在处重叠
our plus W has to be greater than n so
that any W servers must overlap in at
至少一台服务器和我们的任何服务器，所以您可能有三台我们可以
least one server with any our servers
and so you might have three we can
想象有三个服务器s1 s2 s3每个都拥有我说我们只有
imagine there's three servers s1 s2 s3
each of them holds I say we just have
我们正在更新的一个对象发送了一个写操作，也许我们想设置
one object that we're updating we send
out a write maybe we want to set the
我们的对象的值达到23以便进行写入，我们需要获取新的
value of our object to 23 well in order
to do a write we need to get our new
假设至少有W个副本的价值，对于这个系统，
value on to at least W of the of the
replicas let's say for this system that
R和W都等于2，n等于3，这是进行写操作的设置
R and W are both equals 2 and n is equal
to 3 that's the setup to do a write we
需要将我们的新价值变成法定人数，然后变成服务器的野兽，所以也许我们
need to get our new value onto a quorum
onto a beast to the server so maybe we
将我们的权利纳入这两个方面，这样他们俩现在都知道的价值
get our right onto these two so they
both now know that the value of the of
如果有人来读或读它，我们的数据对象是23
our data object is 23 if somebody comes
along and reads or read it also requires
读者至少要检查服务器的法定仲裁数，以便
that the reader check with at least a
read quorum of the servers so that's
在此设置中也包含2个，因此您知道仲裁可能包含一个服务器，
also 2 in this set up so you know that
quorum could include a server that
没有看到正确的权限，但必须至少包含其他权限才能
didn't see the right but it has to
include at least one other in order to
达到这一点意味着任何将来的阅读都必须例如对此进行咨询
get to so that means the any future read
must for example consult both this
没有看到写入的服务器，加上至少有写入的服务器
server that didn't see the write plus at
least one that did
正确形式的要求必须在至少一台服务器中重叠，因此任何
that is a requirement of right form must
overlap in at least one server so any
read必须咨询一台看到以前任何信息的服务器，这很酷
read must consult a server that saw any
previous right now what's cool about
实际上，读者仍然有一个关键的缺失部分
this well actually there's still one
critical missing piece here the reader
将要回来我们的结果可能是不同的结果，因为和
is gonna get back our results possibly
are different results because and the
问题是读者如何知道它从
question is how does a reader know which
of the our results it got back from the
我们在其论坛中的服务器实际上使用了正确的值
our servers in its forum which one
actually uses the correct value
不起作用的事情是投票，就像只是通过
something that doesn't work is voting
like just voting by popularity of the
它返回不同的值，结果证明它不起作用，因为我们只是
different values it gets back it turns
out not to work because we're only
确保我们的读者在最多一台服务器中与作者重叠。
guaranteed that our reader overlaps of
the writer in at most one server so that
可能意味着正确的值仅由其中一台服务器表示
could mean that the correct value is
only represented by one of the servers
读者咨询过，您知道在一个包含六个副本的系统中
that the reader consulted and you know
in a system with say six replicas you
知道您可能有收割者，可能是四岁，您可能会回来寻求答案，并且只有
know you might have Reaper might be four
you might get back for answers and only
其中之一是答案，它是来自服务器的正确答案，其中
one of them is the answer that is the
correct answer from the server in which
您与先前的权利重叠，因此您不能使用投票，而是
you overlap with the previous right so
you can't use voting and instead these
仲裁系统需要版本号，因此每次执行正确操作时都正确
quorum systems need version numbers so
every right every time you do a right
您需要伴随着自己的新价值，并且知道版本不断增加
you need to accompany your new value
with you know an increasing version
数字，然后阅读器从中获取一堆不同的值
number and then the reader it gets back
a bunch of different values from the
读取仲裁，它只能使用我说的最高版本号
read quorum and it can just use them
only the highest version number I'm said
这意味着这里的21可能是s2的旧值
that means that this 21 here
you know maybe s2 had a old value of 20
每个这些都需要标记一个版本号，所以也许这是版本
each of these needs to be tagged with a
version number so maybe this is version
第三，这也是第三版，因为它来自
number three this was also version
number three because it came from the
相同的原始权利，我们正在想象这台服务器没有看到
same original right and we're imagining
that this server that didn't see the
正确的是有第二个版本，那么读者会得到这两个版本
right is gonna have version number two
then the reader gets back these two
值这两个版本号修复的版本是最高值
values these two version numbers fix the
version were the highest the value with
最高版本号，而在Aurora中，这基本上是从来没有
the highest version number and in Aurora
this was essentially about well never
暂时考虑一下Aurora
mind about Aurora for a moment
还可以，如果您不能与您交谈，或者您实际上无法联系法定人数或
okay furthermore if you can't talk to if
you can't actually contact a quorum or a
读或写你真的只需要继续尝试这些规则，所以要保持
read or write you really just have to
keep trying those are the rules so keep
尝试直到服务器的备份或再次连接，所以原因
trying until the server's are brought
back up or connected again so the reason
为什么这比链复制之类的方法更好，是因为它可以轻松地
why this is preferable to something like
chain replication is that it can easily
绕开暂时死机，断开连接或运行缓慢的服务器，实际上是这样
ride out temporary dead or disconnected
or slow servers so in fact the way it
可行的是，如果您想阅读或写作，如果您想写作，
would work is that if you want to read
or write if you want to write you would
说您新写的关于您的东西会发送新写的价值加
saying your newly written about you
would send the newly written value plus
到所有服务器到所有n个服务器的版本号，但仅等待
its version number to all of the servers
to all n of the servers but only wait
让他们中的W做出回应，如果您想阅读，也可以类似地在
for W of them to respond and similarly
if you want to read you would in a
仲裁系统，您将读取发送到所有服务器，并且仅等待
quorum system you would send the read to
all the servers and only wait for a
R的服务器的法定人数作出响应，这是因为您只需要
quorum for R of the servers to respond
and that and because you only have to
等待n个，这意味着您可以在最快的速度后继续
wait for are out of n of them that means
that you can continue after the fastest
已响应或最快的W，而您不必等待服务器运行缓慢
are have responded or the fastest W and
you don't have to wait for a slow server
或一台已死的服务器，您几乎不知道该忽略的机器
or a server that's dead and there's not
any you know the machinery for ignoring
缓慢或死机的服务器是完全隐式的，这里或这里什么都没有
slow or dead servers is completely
implicit there's nothing here or about
哦，我们必须对哪些服务器处于启动或关闭状态做出决策，或者
oh we have to sort of make decisions
about which servers are up or down or
像领导者之类的东西，只要持续很长时间
like the leaders or anything it just
kind of automatically proceeds as long
由于有法定人数，因此我们可以非常平稳地处理死角或缓慢
as the quorum is available so we get
very smooth handling of dead or slow
服务器此外，这里没有太多的回旋余地
servers in addition there's not much
leeway for it here well actually you
即使在这种简单情况下，您也可以调整R和W来读取
even in this simple case you can adjust
the R and W to make either reads to
赞成读或写，所以在这里我们实际上可以说正确
favor either reads or writes so here we
could actually say that well the right
论坛是三个，每个写入都必须转到所有三个服务器，在这种情况下，
forum is three every write has to go to
all three servers and in that case the
可能需要阅读仲裁，因此，如果您希望对此阅读有利
read quorum can be want so you could if
you wanted to favored reads with this
您可能已经读过的设置等于一次写入等于三个内存
setup you could have read equals one
write equals three memories are much
更快，他们只需要等待一台服务器，然后返回写入
faster they only have to wait for one
server but then return the writes are
慢，如果您想赞成，您可以说，任何读者都必须
slow if you wanted to favor right
you could say that Oh any reader has to
来自所有人，但作家只需要写一个，所以我的意思是唯一的一个
be from all of them but a writer only
has to write one so I mean the only one
服务器可能具有最新价值，但读者必须查阅所有三个信息，但
server might have the latest value but
readers have to consult all three but
他们保证他们的三个将与此重叠
they're guaranteed that their three will
overlap with this of course these
特定值使写入不容错，此处读取不容错
particular values makes writes not fault
tolerant and here reads not fault
可以容忍，因为所有服务器都必须启动，所以您可能不想
tolerant because all the server's have
to be up so you probably wouldn't want
要在现实生活中做到这一点，就像Knowle Rohrer所做的那样，
to do this in real life you might have
you would have as Knowle Rohrer does a
服务器数量更多，中间数量的vinum权利
larger number of servers and sort of
intermediate numbers of vinum right
corns Aurora为了能够在这里实现与
corns Aurora in order to achieve its
goals here of being able to write with
一个债务可用区，并读取一个死区和一个可用区
one debt availability zone and read with
one dead availability zone plus one
其他服务器使用仲裁系统，其中N等于6 w等于4并且R等于
other server it uses a quorum system
with N equals 6 w equals 4 and R equals
3，因此W等于4表示它可以使用一个无效的可用区进行写操作
3 so the W equals 4 means that it can do
a write with one dead availability zone
如果不能很好地联系到该可用区域，则其他四台服务器
if this availability zone can't be
contacted well these other four servers
足以完成3则4加上周7的改革，所以他们
are enough to complete right the reform
of 3 so 4 plus week so 7 so they
绝对保证重叠，读取定额为3意味着即使一个
definitely guaranteed overlap a read
quorum of 3 means that even if one
可用性是区域已死，再加上一台服务器，其余三台服务器
availability is zone is dead plus one
more server the three remaining servers
在这种情况下足以供您读取，现在我们的三台服务器已关闭
are enough to serve a read now in this
case we're three servers are now down
该系统可以读取数据，并且您知道可以重建当前范围
the system can do reads and as you know
can reconstruct the confine the current
数据库的状态，但是如果不做进一步的工作就无法写
state of the database but it can't do
writes without further work so if they
当时的情况是
were in a situation where there was
三个死服务器，那里有足够的法定人数，可以读取
three dead servers there they have
enough of a quorum to be able to read
数据并重建更多副本，但是直到它们创建了更多副本为止
the data and reconstruct more cop more
replicas but until they've created more
复制品基本上替代了这些不能用作权利的死者
replicas to basically replace these dead
ones they can't serve as rights
以及我之前解释的仲裁系统使他们可以参加
and also the quorum system as I
explained before allows them to ride out
这些短暂的慢速复制品如发生在发生什么之前一样好
these transient slow replicas all right
as it happens as explained before what
Aurora中的权利并没有真正像在经典著作中那样写东西
the rights in Aurora aren't really over
writing objects as in a sort of classic
仲裁系统Aurora实际上其权利永远不会覆盖其任何内容
quorum system what Aurora in fact its
rights never overwrite anything its
权利只是将日志条目附加到当前法律之后
rights just append log entries to the
current law
因此，使用仲裁的方式基本上可以说是数据库
so the way it's using quorums is
basically to say well when the database
发送新的日志记录，因为它正在执行所需的事务
sends out our new log record because
it's executing some transaction it needs
确保该日志记录至少存在于以下四个存储中
to make sure that that log record is
present on at least four of the store of
允许其继续交易之前的存储服务器是
its storage servers before it's allowed
to proceed with the transaction are
承诺，所以这实际上是其他“*权利”*的意思是
committed so that's really the meaning
of its other Wars right porins is that
每个新的日志记录都必须附加到存储中，至少对于
each new log record has to be appended
to the storage and at least for the
写入之前的副本可以被视为已完成，何时复制
replicas before the write can be
considered to to have completed and when
Aurora在交易结束之前可以回复交易的时间
a when Aurora gets to the end of a
transaction before it can reply to the
客户直到客户告诉客户您好您知道您的交易是
client until the client tell the client
a hi you know your transaction is
承诺，成品和持久性Aurora必须等待确认
committed and finished and durable
Aurora has to wait for acknowledgments
从组成该事务的每个日志记录的仲裁仲裁中
from a write quorum for each of the log
records that made up that transaction
实际上，因为如果恢复中发生崩溃，您就不会
and in fact because because if there
were a crash in a recovery you're not
如果之前的交易也不同，则允许恢复一笔交易
allowed to recover one transaction if
preceding transactions don't aren't also
在Aurora确认交易之前已在实践中恢复
recovered in practice Aurora has before
Aurora can acknowledge a transaction it
必须等待存储服务器的写入定额以响应所有
has to wait for a write quorum of
storage servers to respond for all
先前进行的交易和感兴趣的交易，然后可以
previously committed transaction and the
transaction of interest and then can
回应客户
respond to the client
好的，这些存储服务器正在获取传入的日志记录
okay so these these storage servers are
getting incoming log records
这就是他们的权利，他们实际上知道什么？
that's what rights look like to them and
so what do they actually do you know
他们没有从数据库服务器获取新的数据页面
they're not getting new data pages from
the database server they're just getting
仅描述数据页更改的日志记录，因此在内部是
log records that just describe changes
to the data pages so internally one of
这些存储服务器之一在内部具有所有
these one of these storage servers it
has internally it has copies of all that
数据库中某个时刻所有数据页的数据都会演化，因此
data of all the data pages at some point
in the database data pages evolution so
它的磁盘缓存中可能有一大堆这些您知道的页面
it has maybe in its cache on its disk a
whole bunch of these pages you know page
1页2以此类推，当新的写入操作进入存储服务器时，将赢得一个新的
1 page 2 so forth when a new write comes
in the storage server would win a new
在新的写入中记录的日志记录随它一起携带，只是一个日志记录了什么
log rec over in a new write arrives
carrying with it just a log record what
必须有一天发生，但不是立即发生的是该日志中的更改
has to happen some day but not right
away is that the changes in that log
在这里记录新值必须应用于相关页面，但是我们
record the new value here has to be
applied to the relevant page but we
根本不这样做，直到有人问到
don't at the source of it doesn't have
to do that until someone asks just until
数据库服务器或恢复软件要求查看该页面，因此
the database server or the recovery
software asks to see that page so
立即对新日志记录进行的操作是，日志记录只是
immediately what happens to a new log
record is that the log records are just
附加到影响每个页面的日志记录列表中，因此对于每个页面
appended to lists of log records that
effect each page so for every page that
存储服务器存储是否最近通过日志记录对其进行了修改
the storage server stores if it's been
recently modified by a log record by a
存储服务器实际存储的交易是旧版本的
transaction what the storage server will
actually store is an old version of the
页面以及趋势中出现的日志记录序列的字符串
page plus the string of the sequence of
log records that have come in from trend
自该页面上次更新以来，从数据库服务器访问
from the database server since that page
was last brought up to date so if
没有其他任何情况，存储服务器仅存储这些旧页面以及列表
nothing else happens the storage server
just stores these old pages plus lists
日志记录，如果您以后知道数据库服务器从其修复页面
of log records if the database server
later you know fix the page from its
缓存，然后需要再次读取该页面以进行将来的交易
cache and then needs to read the page
again for a future transaction it'll
向其中一台存储服务器发送读取请求，并说您知道我
send a read request out to one of the
storage servers and say look you know I
需要一份副本，我需要更新副本，一页
need a copy I need an updated copy a
page one
然后存储服务器将这些日志记录应用于页面
and at that point the storage server
will apply these log records to the page
您知道要对这些隐含的新数据进行写操作吗？
you know do do these writes of new data
that are implied that are described in
日志记录，然后将该更新的页面发送回数据库服务器
the log records and then send that
updated page back to the database server
大概就像种族主义者列表一样，只存储新近更新的
and presumably maybe then like a racist
list and just store the newly updated
页面，虽然不是那么简单
page although it's not quite that simple
好的，所以存储服务器只存储这些日志记录字符串以及
all right so the storage servers just
store these strings of log records plus
旧的日志页面版本现在我提到的数据库服务器有时需要
old log page versions now the database
server as I mentioned sometimes needs to
读取页面，因此要观察的一件事是数据库服务器是
read pages so by the way one thing to
observe is that the database server is
写日志记录，但它正在读取数据页，所以我的也有所不同
writing log records but it's reading
data pages so there's also different my
玉米poram系统在某种意义上说是正在被阅读和
corns poram system in the sense that the
sort of things that are being read and
所写的完全不同，此外，事实证明在普通操作中
written are quite different in addition
it turns out that in ordinary operation
数据库服务器知道不必发送仲裁读取，因为
the database server knows doesn't have
to send quorum reads because the
数据库服务器为每个存储服务器跟踪多少存储空间
database server tracks for each one of
the storage servers how far how much of
实际接收到存储服务器的日志的前缀，因此
the prefix of the log that storage
server is actually received so the
数据库服务器正在跟踪这六个数字，因此首先记录
database server is keeping track of
these six numbers so so first of all log
条目仅编号为一二三四五，数据库服务器发送该条目
entries are numbered just one two three
four five the database server sends that
所有存储服务器接收到的所有存储服务器的新日志条目
new log entries to all the storage
servers the storage servers that receive
他们回答说，是的，我收到了日志条目79，此外，您知道我
them respond saying oh yeah I got log
entries 79 and furthermore you know I
在79之前有每个日志条目，数据库服务器也会跟踪这些日志
have every log entry before 79 also the
database server keeps track of these
计算每个服务器已到达的距离或连续的最高状态
numbers how far each server has gotten
or what the highest sort of contiguous
日志条目号是每个服务器都已获得，这样当
log entry number is that each of the
servers has gotten so that way when the
数据库服务器需要进行读取，只需选择一个存储服务器即可
database server needs to do a read it
just picks a storage server that's up to
日期，然后将所需页面的读取请求发送到该存储设备
date and sends the read request for the
page it wants just to that storage
服务器，因此数据库服务器确实必须执行仲裁写入，但是它
server so the the database server does
have to do quorum writes but it
基本上不需要做法定人数
basically
doesn't ordinarily have to do quorum
读取并知道这些存储服务器中的哪些是最新的，并且仅读取
reads and knows which of these storage
servers are up to date and just reads
从他们之一，所以我留给你的理由比他们在一个读
from one of them so the reason I keep ur
than they would be in a that just reads
该页面的一个副本，无需花费一定的法定人数
one copy of the page and doesn't have to
go through the expense of a quorum read
现在它确实有时使用仲裁读取，事实证明在崩溃恢复期间
now it does sometimes use quorum reads
it turns out that during crash recovery
您知道数据库服务器崩溃恢复期间是否崩溃等等
you know if the crash during crash
recovery of the database server and so
这与数据库的崩溃恢复不同，如果数据库
this is different from a crash recovery
of the storage service if the database
服务器本身先生崩溃在我身上，因为它在ec2实例上运行
server itself sir crash in me because
the it's running in an ec2 instance on
某些硬件某些真正的硬件可能就是
some piece of hardware some real piece
of hardware may be that piece of
硬件遭受故障数据库服务器崩溃有一些监控
hardware suffers a failure the database
server crashes there's some monitoring
亚马逊的基础设施说，哦，等等，您知道数据库
infrastructure at Amazon that says oh
wait a minute you know the database the
为客户运行的Aurora数据库服务器或刚崩溃的任何服务器
Aurora database server over running for
a customer or whatever just crashed and
Amazon将自动启动一个新的EC2实例以启动数据库
Amazon will automatically fire up a new
ec2 instance start up the database
软件和该ec2实例，并告诉您您的数据位于
software and that ec2 instance and sort
of tell it look your data is sitting on
此特定数量的存储系统集请清理所有
this particular volume this set of
storage systems please clean up any
存储在这些文件中的日志中明显可见的部分执行的事务
partially executed transactions that are
evident in the logs stored in these
存储服务器，然后继续，所以我们必须这样做，这就是Aurora的重点
storage servers and continue so we have
to and that's the point at which Aurora
对杂草使用定额逻辑，因为此数据库服务器当旧时
uses quorum logic for weeds because this
database server when the old when the
以前的数据库服务器崩溃了，几乎肯定是在途中
previous database server crashed it was
almost certainly partway through
执行一些交易，以便在交易发生时
executing some set of transactions so
the state of play at the time of the
崩溃很好，它完成了一些事务并提交了它们，
crash was well it's completed some
transactions and committed them and
他们的日志条目已达到法定人数，而且正在执行一些
their log entries are on a quorum plus
it's in the middle of executing some
其他交易集，也可能在法定人数上有日志条目，但是
other set of transactions which also may
have log entries on on a quorum but
因为数据库服务器在进行这些事务的过程中崩溃了，所以他们可以
because a database server crashed midway
through those transactions they can
永远不会完成，对于那些尚未完成的交易
never be completed and for those
transactions that haven't completed in
此外，也许您知道我们可能遇到一种情况，您可能知道
addition there may be you know we may
have a situation in which you know maybe
日志条目此服务器已登录三百
log entry this server has log on three
hundred
萨里（Surrey）登录302，某个地方有一百零四，但没有
and the Surrey has logon 302 and there's
a hundred and four somewhere but no you
在崩溃让我知道之前我还没有提交交易
know for I as yet uncommitted
transaction before the crash made me
知道服务器获得了日志条目103的副本，因此在崩溃后记住了新的
know server got a copy of log entry 103
so after a crash and remember the new
恢复它的数据库服务会进行仲裁读取，以基本找到要点
database service recovering it does
quorum reads to basically find the point
日志中存在每个先前日志条目的最高日志号
in the log the highest log number for
which every preceding log entry exists
在存储服务中的某个位置，因此基本上可以找到第一个缺少的
somewhere in the storage service so
basically it finds the first missing the
第一个丢失的日志条目的编号是103，表示正确，因此我们
number of the first missing log entry
which is 103 and says well and so we're
缺少日志条目之后，我们将无法对日志执行任何操作，因为
missing a log entry we can't do anything
with a log after this point because
我们就像错过更新，因此数据库服务器执行这些法定读取
we're like missing an update so the
database server does these quorum reads
它发现一百零三是MIT的第一个条目，我无法
it finds a hundred and three is the
first entry that's MIT that's I can't
你知道我看我的仲裁服务器可以达到的，而103不是
you know I look at my quorum the
server's I can reach and 103 is not
在那里，数据库服务器将向所有服务器发送一条消息，说
there and the database server will send
out a message to all the server saying
看，请丢弃从103开始的所有日志条目，以及那些贻贝
look please just discard every log entry
from 103 onwards and those mussels
不一定包含已提交交易的日志条目，因为我们知道
necessarily not include log entries from
committed transactions because we know a
在所有条目都在右上角之前，事务无法提交
transaction can't commit until all of
its entries are on a right corner so we
一定会看到它们，因此我们仅丢弃来自
would be guaranteed to see them so we're
only discarding log entries from
当然是未提交的交易，因此我们有点在这里切断日志
uncommitted transactions of course so
we're sort of cutting off the log here
在登录302处，我们现在保留的这些日志条目实际上可能
at login 302 these log entries that
we're preserving now may actually
包括来自未提交事务的日志条目，这些事务来自
include log entries from uncommitted
transactions from transactions that were
由于崩溃而中断，数据库服务器实际上必须检测
interrupted by the crash and the
database server actually has to detect
通过看到希望可以知道某笔交易可以做到的
those which you can by seeing a hope you
know a certain transaction there's it
日志中有更新条目，但没有提交记录，数据库服务器将
has update entries in the log but no
commit record the database server will
查找未完成交易的全部内容，然后基本上撤消
find the full set of those uncompleted
transactions and basically issue undo
我了解了一些日志条目，这些操作撤消了所有的更改，
operations I sort of knew log entries
that undo all of the changes that that
这些未提交的交易，您知道这就是
that those uncommitted transactions made
and you know that's the point at which
Aurora需要在日志条目中使用这些旧值，以便
Aurora needs this these old values in
the log entries so that a
崩溃后正在恢复的服务器可能会部分退出
server that's doing recovery after a
crash can sort of back out of partially
我想谈论的另一件事是完成交易
completed transactions all right one
another thing I'd like to talk about is
到目前为止，Aurora如何处理大型数据库
how Aurora deals with big databases so
so far I've explained the storage setup
好像数据库只有其存储的这六个副本，如果
as if the database just has these six
replicas of its storage and if that was
基本上所有的内容都不可能是数据库，您不知道其中的每一个
all there was to it basically a database
couldn't be you know each of these just
装有一个或两个磁盘的计算机，如果有的话
a computer with a disk or two or
something attached to it if this were
这样的话，我们就无法拥有更大的数据库
the way the full situation then we
couldn't have a database that was bigger
比您在一台计算机上可以放置的存储量多
than the amount of storage that you
could put on a single machine there's
我们拥有六台机器的事实并不能为我们提供六倍的可用率
the fact that we have six machines
doesn't give us six times as much usable
之所以要存储，是因为我每个人都在再次存储相同旧数据的副本，
storage because each one I'm storing a
replica of the same old data again and
再次，你知道，所以我想使用固态驱动器或一些我们可以
again and you know so I want to use
solid-state drives or something we can
让您知道一台计算机上的TB级存储，但是我们不能让您知道
put you know terabytes of storage on a
single machine but we can't put you know
一台机器上数百​​TB的数据，以便支持客户
hundreds of terabytes on a single
machine so in order to support customers
需要超过十亿兆字节的数据，需要拥有庞大的数据库
who need like more than ten terabytes
who need to have vast databases Amazon
感到高兴的是，亚马逊将把数据库数据分成了六组
is happy Amazon will split up the
databases data onto multiple sets of six
这样复制和分片的单元的种类
replicas so and the kind of unit of
sharding the unit of splitting up the
我认为是10 GB的数据，所以需要20 GB数据的数据库
data I think is 10 gigabytes so a
database that needs 20 gigabytes of data
您将使用两个保护组将这些PG事物用于这些数据，
will use two protection groups these
these PG things to its data you know sit
其中一半将位于第一保护组的​​六台服务器上，然后
on half of it will sit on the six
servers of protection Group one and then
他们将是另外六个服务器，您可能知道一组不同的六个存储
they'll be another six servers you know
possibly a different set of six storage
服务器，因为亚马逊正在运行，并且像这些存储的庞大团队一样
servers because Amazon's running and
like a huge fleet of these storage
由其所有Aurora客户共同使用的服务器，第二个十个
servers that are jointly used by all of
its Aurora customers the second ten
数据库的20 GB数据
gigabytes of the databases 20 gigabytes
of data
我们将复制到另一组您身上，通常您会有所不同，我会
we'll be replicated on another set of
you know typically different I'll you
知道这些之间可能有重叠，但通常只是一组不同
know there could be overlap between
these but typically just a different set
六台服务器，因此现在我们一天可以完成20 GB的存储，而我们还有更多
of six server so now we get 20 gigabytes
a day done and we have more of these as
数据库变得更大，一个有趣的后果是，
a database goes bigger one interesting
piece of fallout from this is that while
显然，您可以获取数据页并将其拆分为多个
it's clear that you can take the data
pages and split them up over multiple
独立的保护组，也许您知道您的奇数数据页
independent protection groups maybe you
know odd numbered data pages from your
b树在PG上运行，甚至页数也在PG上-可以分片是很好的
b-tree go on PG one and even number
pages go on PG - it's good you can shard
拆分数据页面并不清楚如何处理
split up the data pages it's not
immediately obvious what to do with a
正确记录日志如果您有两个，如何拆分日志
log all right how do you split up the
log if you have two of these two
保护小组或更多保护小组以及答案，亚马逊
protection groups or more in a mantra
tection group and the answer that amazon
的确是Aurora使用的是数据库服务器
does is that that that Aurora uses is
that the database server when it's
发送日志记录，它查看日志记录修改的数据，
sending out a log record it looks at the
data that the log record modifies and
找出哪些保护组存储该数据并发送每个日志
figures out which protection groups
store that data and it sends each log
仅记录到存储提到的数据的保护组中
record just to the protection groups
that store data that's mentioned that's
在日志条目中进行了修改，这意味着这些保护中的每一个
modified in the log entry and so that
means that each of these protection
组存储部分数据页以及所有的日志记录
groups store some fraction of the data
pages plus all the log records that
适用于这些数据页，请参阅这些保护组存储的一个子集
apply to those data pages see these
protection groups stores a subset of a
与其页面相关的日志，所以最终我可能会擦除光子
log that's relevant to its pages so a
final maybe I erase the photons
要求，但最终要求是，如果这些存储之一
requirements but a final requirement is
that if a if ass one of these storage
服务器崩溃，我们希望能够尽快将其替换对
servers crashes we want to be able to
replace it as soon as possible right
因为您知道如果我们等待太久，那么我们可能会冒险三个
because you know if we wait too long
then we risk maybe three of them are
其中四个崩溃了，其中四个崩溃了，那么我们实际上无法恢复
four of them crashing and a four of them
crash then we actually can't recover
因为那样的话我们就没有改革了，所以我们需要重新获得复制
because then we don't have a reform
anymore so we need to regain replication
如果您考虑使用任何一台存储服务器，请尽快确保这样做
as soon as possible if you think about
any one storage server sure this this do
您知道哪个服务器存储10 GB的数据，我的数据库保护组
which server is storing 10 gigabytes for
you know my databases protection group
但实际上，您知道其中任何一项的物理设置
but in fact the physical thing you know
the physical setup of any one of these
服务器是它有一个，你可能知道一个或两个
servers is that it has a you know maybe
a one or two or something
兆兆字节的磁盘，它存储100个或更多的10 GB分段
terabyte disk on it that's storing 10
gigabyte segments of a hundred or more
不同的Aurora实例，那么您在这台物理计算机上是什么
different Aurora instances so what's
what's on this physical machine is you
知道10 TB时代字节或10 TB或总计的数据量
know 10 terabyte era byte or 10
terabytes or whatever of data in total
因此，当这些存储服务器之一发生崩溃时，
so when there's a when one of these
storage servers crashes it's taking with
它不仅是我数据库中的10 GB，而且还是我的数据库中的10 GB
it not just the 10 gigabytes from my
database but also 10 gigabytes from a
一百个其他人的数据库，必须复制的不是
hundred other people's databases as well
and what has to be replicated is not
只有我的10 GB，但是整个TB或更多
just my 10 gigabytes but the entire
terabyte or whatever or more that's
存储在此服务器固态驱动器上，如果您仔细考虑一下数字，
stored on this servers solid-state drive
and if you think through the numbers you
知道如果我们需要移动10个，每秒可能有10 GB的网络接口
know maybe we have 10 gigabit per second
network interfaces if we need to move 10
每秒10 GB的网络接口中的1 TB
terabytes across a 10 gigabyte per
second network interface from one
机器到另一个要花的时间我不知道一千秒十
machine to another it's gonna take I
don't know a thousand seconds ten
一千秒或一万秒，那太长了
thousand seconds maybe ten thousand
seconds and that's way too long right we
不想坐在那里等着你知道我们不想有一个
don't want to have to sit there and wait
you know it we don't want to have a
我们可以弱化我们可以重建它的方法的策略是找到
strategy in which the way we weak we can
reconstruct this is to find is to have
另一台正在复制所有内容并拥有该机器的机器
another machine that was replicating
everything on it and had that machine
发送10 TB到替换机器，我们将能够
send 10 terabytes to a replacement
machine we're gonna be able to
重建数据的速度远比重建数据快，因此它们使用的实际设置是
reconstruct the data far faster than
that and so the actual setup they use is
如果我有一台特定的存储服务器
that if I have a particular storage
server
它存储了许多段，您知道许多10 GB保护的副本
it stores many many segments you know
replicas of many 10 gigabyte protection
组，所以也许这个保护组也许是它存储的这个细分市场
groups so maybe this protection group
maybe this segment that it's storing
另一个羡慕的数据，另一个副本是吗，您知道这五个
data for the other envy for this one the
other replicas are you know these five
其他机器好了，这些都存储了
保护组A的各个部分，所以您知道还有很多其他
我们也要存储的那些，所以我的意思是我们也可能是这台特定的机器
ones that we're also storing so I mean
we may be this particular machine also
存储用于保护组B的副本，但存储B数据的其他副本
将被放置在一组不相交的服务器上，所以现在有五个
are going to be put on a disjoint set of
servers right so now there's five
具有B的其他副本的服务器，以此类推。
servers that have the other copies of B
and so on for all of the segments that
您知道此服务器位于此存储服务器的硬盘驱动器上
许多很多不同的Aurora实例，这意味着这台机器宕机了
many many different Aurora instances so
that means that this machine goes down
替换策略是选择是否要存储100个
the replacement strategy is that we pick
if we're say we're storing a hundred of
这些细分市场上，我们选择了一百个不同的存储服务器，每个
将要选择一个新的细分市场，每个细分市场现在都将成为
is gonna pick up one new segment that is
each of which is going to now be
参加另外一个保护小组，所以我们像一个服务器一样错过了一个
可以复制到这十个千兆字节的段中的每一个，现在我们有了
to be replicate on for each of these ten
gigabytes segments and now we have you
知道大概100种不同的段服务器，您可能知道我在存储
know maybe 100 sort of different segment
servers and you know I probably storing
其他东西，但它们有一点可用磁盘空间，然后每个
这些我们选择一台机器，我们将要复制的副本之一
these we pick one machine one of the
replicas that we're going to copy the
来自剩余副本之一的数据，所以也许对于
data from one of the remaining replicas
so maybe for a we're going to copy from
从这里到B，你知道我们是否还有五个C副本，我们选择一个
there for B from here you know if we
have five other copies with C we pick a
C的其他服务器，因此我们将a从该服务器复制到该服务器
different server for C and so we have we
copy a from this server to that server
和B像这样，C像这样，所以现在我们有一百个不同的10
and B like this and C like this and so
now we have a hundred different 10
千兆字节副本在网络上并行运行，并且假设您知道
gigabyte copies going on in parallel
across the network and assuming you know
我们有足够的服务器，这些服务器都可以脱节，并且我们有很多
we have enough servers that these can
all be disjoint and we have plenty of
连接它们的交换网络的带宽现在我们可以复制我们的
bandwidth in switching network that
connects them now we can copy our
TB或10 TB或任何数据，总计与一个并行
terabyte or 10 terabytes or whatever of
data and total in parallel with a
百倍并行度，整个过程将花费您10秒钟的时间，或者
hundredfold parallelism and the whole
thing will take you know 10 seconds or
如果只有两台机器，则无需花费一千秒
something instead of taking a thousand
seconds if there were just two machines
无论如何，所以这就是他们使用的策略，
involved anyway so this is
this is the strategies they use and it
意味着他们可以恢复，因为他们知道可以恢复机器死机
means that they can recover you know for
machine dies they can recover in
如果有很多机器，那么从一台机器的死亡中很快就可以并行
parallel from one machine's death
extremely quickly if lots of machines
节食效果不好，但可以从单身中恢复
diets doesn't work as well but they can
recover from single they can be
从单台计算机复制崩溃会很快崩溃，所以最终
replicate from single machine crashes
extremely quickly alright so a final
如果您看图三，该论文提到的内容将不会
thing that the paper mentions if you
look at figure three you'll see that not
他们只有这个主数据库，但也有副本数据库，因此
only do they have this main database but
they also have replica databases so for
许多客户许多客户看到更多的只读查询
many of their customers many of their
customers see far more read-only queries
比他们看到的读写查询（如果您考虑使用Web服务器）
than they see readwrite queries that is
if you think about a web server if you
只需在某些网站上查看网页，那么您的网络服务器就很可能
just view a web page on some website
then chances are the web server you
连接到必须阅读很多很多东西以生成所有
connected to has to read lots and lots
and stuff in order to generate all the
页面上显示给您的东西可能有数百种
things that are shown on the page to you
maybe hundreds of different items have
从数据库中读出或从某个数据库中读出，但是
to be read out of the database or so out
of some database but the number of
为典型的网页视图编写的内容通常要小得多，也许有些
writes for a typical web page view is
usually much much smaller maybe some
您必须更新统计信息或一些历史记录
statistics have to be updated or a
little bit of history for you or
某件事，所以您可能拥有100：1的读写比
something so you might have a hundred to
one ratio of reads to writes that is you
通常可能具有大量的大量直接只读数据库
may typically have a large large large
number of straight read only database
现在使用此设置进行查询，写入只能通过一个数据库
queries now with this set up the writes
can only go through the one database
服务器，因为我们实际上只能为此存储支持一个编写器
server because we really can only
support one writer for this storage
策略，我想您知道橡胶真正发挥作用的地方
strategy and I think you know one place
where the rubber really hits the road
日志条目必须按顺序编号，这很容易
there is that the log entries have to be
numbered sequentially and that's easy to
如果所有写入都通过一台服务器，并且如果我们
do if all the writes go through a single
server and extremely difficult if we
有很多不同的服务器，它们以不协调的方式编写
have lots of different servers all sort
of writing in an uncoordinated way to
同一数据库，因此写操作实际上必须通过一个数据库进行，但是
the same database so the writes really
have to be go through one database but
我们可以设置，实际上亚马逊确实设置了一种情况，我们已经阅读
we could set up and indeed Amazon does
set up a situation where we have read
仅可以从这些存储服务器读取的数据库副本，因此
only database replicas that can read
from these storage servers and so the
图三的全部荣耀是，除了主数据库服务器
full glory of figure three is that in
addition to the main database server
处理写请求，还有一组只读
that handles the write requests there's
also a set of read-only
数据库，他们说它们最多可以支持15个，因此您实际上可以获得很多
databases and they say they can support
up to 15 so you can actually get a lot
你们当中的人知道，如果您的上级会给您带来很多工作量，
of you know if your senior we'd have you
workload a lot of it can be you know
大部分都可以分解为一大堆这些只读数据库
most of it can be sort of hived off to a
whole bunch of these read-only databases
当客户端发送读取请求以只读数据库时，会发生什么情况
and when a client sends a read request
to read only database what happens is
只读数据库表明您知道它需要服务哪些数据页
the read only database figures out you
know what data pages it needs to serve
该请求并将读取直接发送到存储系统，而无需
that request and sends reads into the
directly into the storage system without
麻烦主读写数据库，以便只读副本数据库
bothering the main readwrite database so
the the read-only replica database
升序页面请求直接在存储服务器上读取请求，然后
ascend page requests read requests
directly the storage servers and then
它们将不会缓存这些页面，以便您可以知道它们对将来的读取做出响应
they'll be no cache those pages so that
they can you know respond to future read
当然需要从缓存中获取请求，他们需要能够更新
requests right out of their cache of
course they need to be able to update
这些缓存，因此Aurora也会在主数据库中发送一份副本
those caches and for that reason Aurora
also the main database sends a copy of
它的日志到每个只读数据库，这就是水平
its log to each of the read-only
databases and that's the horizontal
您在蓝色框和图三之间看到的线是主数据库
lines you see between the blue boxes and
figure three that the main database
发送所有日志条目，这意味着仅用于更新的数据库
sends all the log entries do these mean
only databases which they use to update
它们的缓存副本以反映数据库及其中的最近事务
their cached copies to reflect recent
transactions in the database and it
意味着它确实意味着只读数据库落后于
means it does mean that the read only
database is lag a little bit behind the
主数据库，但事实证明，对于许多只读工作负载，如果
main database but it turns out for a lot
of read-only workloads that's okay if
您看一个网页，就知道过了20毫秒
you look at a web page and it's you know
20 milliseconds out of date that's
通常不是一个大问题，像这样一个问题会带来一些复杂性
usually not a big problem there are some
complexities from this like one problem
是我们不希望这些中继数据库看到未提交的数据
is that we don't want these relay
databases to see data from uncommitted
事务尚未完成，因此在此日志条目流中，数据库可能需要
transactions yet and so in this stream
of log entries the database may need to
有点表示已提交哪些事务，并且它们是只读的
be sort of denotes which transactions
have committed and they're read-only
数据库小心不要应用不常见
databases are careful not to apply
uncommon
未提交的事务到其缓存中，他们等待直到提交事务
uncommitted transactions to their caches
they wait till the transactions commit
这些只读副本带来的另一个复杂性是
the other complexity that these
read-only replicas impose is that
这些和这些结构的这些结构非常复杂
the the the these structures he of these
andhe structures are quite complex this
可能是b树，可能需要定期重新平衡，例如
might be a b-tree it might need to be
rebalanced periodically for example I'm
重新平衡是一个非常复杂的操作，其中很多树都有
the rebalancing is quite a complex
operation in which a lot of the tree has
被原子地修改，因此树在被修改时是不正确的
to be modified in atomically and so the
tree is incorrect while it's being be
平衡，并且只有在重新平衡完成后，如果
balanced and you only allowed to look at
it after the rebalancing is done if
这些只读副本直接从数据库中读取页面，其中有一个
these read-only replicas directly read
the pages out of the database there's a
冒着风险，他们可能会看到存储在此处的数据库的树
risk they might see the be tree that the
database that's being stored here in
这些数据页在重新平衡过程中可能会看到蜂树，或者
these data pages they may see the bee
tree in the middle of a rebalancing or
其他操作，数据完全是非法的，他们可能
some other operation and the data is
just totally illegal and they might
崩溃或仅仅是故障，以及当报纸谈论迷你交易和
crash or just malfunction and when the
paper talks about mini transactions and
vdl与vcl的区别在于它所指的是机器
the vdl verses vcl distinction what it's
talking about is the machinery by which
数据库服务器可以告诉存储服务器看这个复杂的序列
the database server can tell the storage
servers look this complex sequence of
日志条目必须仅对所有只读对象显示全部或不显示
log entries must only be revealed all or
nothing' atomically to any read-only
迷你交易和VDL所涉及的交易以及
transactions that's what the mini
transactions and VDL are about and
基本上是只读数据库要求查看数据数据页时的读取
basically the read when a read only
database asks to see data a data page
来自存储服务器的存储服务器要小心，要么显示来自
from a storage server the storage server
is careful to either show it data from
在这些序列之一之前，有许多日志条目的事务序列，或者
just before one of these sequence many
transaction sequences of log entries or
就在中间但不在中间好吧，这就是所有技术
just after but not in the middle all
right so that's the all the technical
我必须谈论的东西只是总结一些有趣的东西
stuff I have to talk about just to kind
of summarize what's interesting about
论文以及可以从论文中学到的东西
the paper and what can be learned from
the paper one thing to learn which is
总体上来说还不错，但不是专门针对本文，而是系统中的每个人
just good in general not specific to
this paper but everybody in systems
应该知道的是事务处理数据库如何工作的基础
should know is the basics of how
transaction processing databases work
以及交易之间相互作用的那种影响
and the sort of impact that the
interaction between transaction
处理数据库和存储系统，因为这很多
processing databases and the storage
systems because this comes up a lot it's
像无所不在一样，您知道性能和崩溃可恢复性
like a pervasive you know the
performance and crash recoverability
运行真实数据库的复杂性一遍又一遍地出现
complexity of running a real database
just comes up over and over again in
系统设计本文要学习的另一件事是定额和
systems design another thing to learn
this paper is this idea of quorums and
为了始终保持重叠，将重叠的读/写仲裁的技术重叠
overlap the technique of overlapping
read/write quorums in order to always be
能够查看最新数据，但还能获得容错能力，这当然可以
able to see the latest data but also get
fault tolerance and of course this comes
在木筏上，木筏也具有很强的法定风味
up in raft also raft has a strong kind
of quorum flavor to it
本文的另一个有趣的想法是数据库和
another interesting thought from this
paper is that the database and the
存储系统基本上是Co设计为一种集成的
storage system are basically Co designed
as kind of an integrated there's
跨数据库层和存储层的集成或几乎
integration across the database layer
and the storage layer or nearly
重新设计以尝试设计系统，以便它们使您知道良好的分离
redesigned to try to design systems so
they have you know good separation
服务使用者与诸如
between consumers of services and the
sort of infrastructure services like
通常，存储是非常通用的，而不是针对
typically storage is very
general-purpose not aimed at a
您知道特定的应用程序，因为这是一个令人愉快的设计
particular application just you know
because that's a pleasant design and it
也意味着同一基础架构可以有很多不同的用途
also means that lots of different uses
can be made of the same infrastructure
但是这里的性能问题是如此极端，以至于您必须知道
but here the performance issues were so
extreme you know they would have to get
通过模糊此边界将性能提高了35倍，这是
a 35 times performance improvement by
sort of blurring this boundary this was
通用存储实际上不是这样的情况
a situation in which general-purpose
storage was actually really not
优势，他们放弃了这个想法，最终获得了巨大的胜利。
advantageous and they got a big win by
abandoning that idea and a final set of
事情从论文中脱颖而出所有有趣的有时是隐含的
things to get out of the papers all the
interesting sometimes kind of implicit
有关对您认识的这些亚马逊工程师有价值的信息
information about what was valuable to
these Amazon engineers who you know
真的知道他们在做什么，他们对云有什么担忧
really know what they're doing about
what concerns they had about cloud
基础设施，例如他们担心的可能性
infrastructure like the amount of worry
that they put into the possibility of an
整个可用区可能会失败，这是一个重要的提示，
entire availability zone might fail it's
an important tidbit the fact that
各个存储服务器的暂时缓慢很重要是另一回事
transient slowness of individual storage
servers was important is another thing
实际上也出现了很多，最后暗示了网络
that actually also comes up a lot and
finally the implication that the network
是主要瓶颈，因为毕竟他们付出了极大的努力
is the main bottleneck because after all
they were it went to extreme lengths to
通过网络发送较少的数据，但作为回报，存储服务器具有
send less data over the network
but in return the storage servers have
做更多的工作，他们说，他们愿意知道6份数据
to do more work and they put it they're
willing to you know 6 copies the data
并有6个CPU都复制了应用这些重做日志的执行
and have 6 CPUs all replicating the
execution of applying these redo log
条目显然对他们来说CPU相对便宜，而网络
entries apparently CPU is relatively
cheap for them whereas the network
能力是非常重要的，好吧，我必须说的是
capacity was extremely important
all right that's all I have to say and
下周见
see you next week